<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Khalid&#39;s Shell</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Khalid&#39;s Shell</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 16:01:22 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Desktop Extensions in Firefox for Android</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/firefox-android-desktop-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 15:17:22 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/firefox-android-desktop-extensions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Firefox offers a wide range of extensions that enhance browsing on desktop, but many of these are not officially available on Android. Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s a workaround to install desktop extensions on Firefox for Android. Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;steps-to-install-desktop-extensions&#34;&gt;Steps to Install Desktop Extensions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enable the Debug Menu&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Open Firefox on your Android device.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Go to &lt;strong&gt;Settings&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;About Firefox&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Tap the Firefox logo &lt;strong&gt;7 times&lt;/strong&gt; to enable the &lt;strong&gt;Debug Menu&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Download the Extension&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Code Without a Computer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/coding-without-computer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 00:05:03 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/coding-without-computer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Many people want to learn programming but can&amp;rsquo;t because they don&amp;rsquo;t have a computer. Good news for them: you can learn programming using just your mobile phone. Let’s see how:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-online-code-editors-and-compilers&#34;&gt;1. Online Code Editors and Compilers:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The easiest way to code on a mobile device is by using online code editors and compilers. Search for terms like &lt;em&gt;online code editor&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;online compiler&lt;/em&gt; in your search engine (or ask an AI chatbot), and you’ll find many options, such as &lt;a href=&#34;http://codepen.io/&#34;&gt;CodePen&lt;/a&gt;, which is a front-end web development environment. The advantage is that you can code directly from your browser without installing any additional apps. Even if your mobile device isn’t high-end, you can still manage. However, your phone must support internet browsing. If you struggle to find a code editor or compiler that supports your programming language, try searching with the specific programming language name.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux Frozen? Recover and Troubleshoot System Issues with SysRq Commands</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/sysrq-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 00:05:03 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/sysrq-linux/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Linux &lt;strong&gt;SysRq&lt;/strong&gt; commands are a lifesaver when your system freezes or becomes unresponsive. The kernel always responds to these commands, no matter what state the computer is in. However, if the kernel itself is completely locked up, that&amp;rsquo;s a different story. The &lt;strong&gt;SysRq&lt;/strong&gt; feature is extremely useful when system issues occur. For example, if your Linux is frozen and stops responding to any input, you can use &lt;strong&gt;SysRq&lt;/strong&gt; command to shut down or reboot the computer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
